hey there everyone welcome to the first
ever Timbers one-two-three-four-five
interview let's get started shall we
first off I would like to make things
clear [ __ ] I do not answer every
question I merely picked out at which
ones I thought everyone would want to
have answered now let us move on to the
first question why do you like rock
Underground so much well that's an easy
one [ __ ] because it's bitchin
it's perfect in every way don't let
anyone tell you otherwise question
number two where I'll Sleet Dingo and
Robotnik in your videos you don't seem
to show them much love I don't have a
complete answer at the moment but what I
can say here is they might appear
sometime you gotta understand as a
professional animator I don't want to
just shove kids in for no reason that
will only hurt the overall story being
told so I would like to wait for a good
time in place for it to happen
question number three where did you get
the box for your cosplay will you make a
coil of how you make it no I won't this
is a one of a kind and as you can tell
it's now a what a box is many boxes put
together the way I got the boxes is you
see my local came out down the street
every Friday or some [ __ ] they thought
some boxes I just walk up and say sup
I'm Tim was one three four five and then
they just give me the boxes because they
know I like to make costumes with them
sometimes me and the ploys would even
make costumes together which reminds me
I even have a mana costume in the works
question number four
why do you ships narcan Bobby so much I
think that's pretty obvious watch the
show and see for yourself [ __ ] question
number five what's your least hear talk
op so I don't got none
Ghanim [ __ ] can I hear question
number six
have you ever did drugs with Knuckles
you see I don't do drugs
and neither does not cause me and my
friend Sonic Manic Sonia all of us
really we all go by one simple rule when
it comes to that [ __ ] if you want to be
cool don't do drugs stay in school and
then you're cool question number seven
how old is your Bobby costume [ __ ] do
you not watch my videos I mean have you
watched my birthday that's what I get
the [ __ ] costume and I'm the only
here in this [ __ ] you need to watch my
[ __ ] you I ask me questions if you
haven't watched my videos can't get out
of it so beat your ass
follow BR question number eight
do you have a job if so then what is it
if not how do you get back well I
thought it was pretty obvious well
apparently not [ __ ] oh I'm demons 1 2 3
4 5 all I need to do is walk outside say
hey everyone I'm teams 1 3 4 5
give me your marlane maybe we'll just
throw money at my ass I mean I'm
basically like I'm famous so then that's
kind of what we famous people do
question number nine why do you think so
many people overlook su I think it's
because Sonic Underground was cancelled
out of the first few episodes so they
never really got to see the entire show
it is the [ __ ] [ __ ] if you watch the
whole show I mean you gotta understand
this wasn't al where YouTube didn't
exist you couldn't watch Sonic
Underground episodes on the internet you
had to go and buy that [ __ ] that's all
for today everyone tomorrow I'll be
going through the final few questions a
lot of them are pretty cool so get hot
and always remember
sockin will always love you